Inventory of the John Ehrlichman Papers, 1963-1982
Hoover Institution Archives
- AUDIOVISUAL FILE, Appendix B - John Ehrlichman Media Tapes Dating from 1/30/71 to 7/30/78 (Box 4-17)
  - "Watergate" TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 6/17/77 (Tape 192)
  - "HRH-JM-Watergate" 2 Sides, 6/21-22/77 (Tape 193)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS", Program #1, 2 Sides - Edited, 9/6/77 (Tape 194)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS" Program #2, 2 Sides - Edited (Tape 195)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS" Program #3, 2 Sides - Edited, 9/8/77 (Tape 196)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS" Program #4, 2 Sides - Edited, 9/9/77 (Tape 197)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS" Program #5, 2 Sides - Edited, 9/10/77 (Tape 198)
  - "BEHIND CLOSED DOORS" Final Program #6, 2 Sides - Edited, 9/11/77 (Tape 199)
  - John D. Sirica (Judge), on John Ehrlichman/John Mitchell, H. R. Haldeman, 10/4/77 (Tape 200)
  - John Ehrlichman. Parole recommendation, 12/77; Ray Price interviews/Jack Anderson on JE, 12/9/77 (Tape 201)
  - Ray Price, with Tom Snyder NBC TV, 12/14/77 (Tape 202)
  - News broadcasts relating to JE divorce, ca. 1978 (Tape 203)
  - "Haldeman Book" TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 2/16-17/78 (Tape 204)
  - Charles Colson, Phil Donahue Show NBC TV, 2 Sides, 3/13/78 (Box 17, Tape 205)
  - J. E., 2 Sides, 4/29/78-4/30/78 (Tape 206)
  - RN Book, 5/1/78
  - ....RN Book/John Ehrlichman, TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 5/1-4/78 (Tape 207)
  - "RN-JE" TV Capsules, 2 Sides, 5/5-27/78 (Tape 208)
  - RN Book/etc. and recent, 2 Sides, 5/13/78 (Tape 209)
  - JE, 7/27/78; Watergate, 7/30/78 (Tape 210)
  - John Ehrlichman, Watergate Hearings/, Part Two NET and Network, 2 Sides, 7/30/78 (Tape 211)
- Incremental Materials - CLOSED (Box 18-137)